Contact

Zielonka (Biale Blota), kujwaskopomorskie, Polska +48 602522030 (Mobile) marcin.tubielewicz@gmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/ marcintubielewicz (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

PostgreSQL deployment on Ubuntu Advanced configuration and tuning of PostgreSQL

Problem diagnosis and resolution in PostgreSQL environments

Languages

german: C1 (Limited Working) english: B2 (Limited Working)

Certifications

ISTQB Certyfikowany tester - poziom podstawowy

Negocjacje zakupowe
Data Science & Machine Learning
Negocjacje zakupowe
Al Agents Fundamentals

Marcin Tubielewicz

Technology enthusiast with extensive experience and advanced technical, analytical and interpersonal skills, ready to collaborate on the success of your company.

Białe Błota, Kujawsko-pomorskie, Poland

Summary

I am an experienced professional whose approach to work harmonizes extensive professional experience with a passion for technology and knowledge acquired during my studies in computer science and business. Thanks to my accumulated experience, openness to new challenges and constant striving for development, I excel in a wide variety of fields.

My professional portfolio is very diverse, encompassing both solid technical skills, data analysis and interpersonal skills. I excel in difficult situations that require quick decisions, and my communication skills are key in both customer/supplier relationships and effective teamwork.

Currently, I am expanding the education I have recently acquired by developing my skills in the broad field of BigData. One of the achievements in this area is a self-built cluster, with the help of which I am developing my competence in Apache Spark, Apache Hadoop, HDFS technologies, or Java and Scala programming languages, as well as the Linux operating system itself.

Experience

Belma Accessories Systems Sp. z o.o. 18 years

IT Consultant March 2024 - Present (1 year 3 months) Białe Błota, Woj. Kujawsko-Pomorskie, Polska

Conducting business requirements analysis, planning the implementation of new systems and technologies, developing IT strategies supporting the organization's business goals, creating technical documentation and operational procedures, planning and coordinating IT projects, monitoring project progress, managing project resources, ensuring compliance of

activities with the schedule and budget. Organization and participation in the process of implementing artificial intelligence solutions in the enterprise from the conceptual phase to final implementation.

independent specialist September 2021 - March 2024 (2 years 7 months)

Białe Błota

analysis of suppliers and market trends by monitoring the market and product prices, creating and maintaining a database of raw material prices and key company KPIs in the field of steel materials, forecasting behavior, reporting data, presenting trends and prices using MS Excel and Power BI. From September '23, temporarily delegated to support the IT department in the field of building and maintaining company infrastructure, monitoring security systems, installation and configuration of systems and computer equipment

manager of metallurgical products section October 2018 - August 2021 (2 years 11 months)

Białe Błota

managing the team, planning delivery schedules, managing the purchasing process to ensure the continuity of the company's production processes, monitoring the level of raw materials and materials. Ensure compliance with standards and regulations and improve purchasing processes

purchasing manager April 2015 - September 2018 (3 years 6 months) Białe Błota

managing a team, organizing the work of own and subordinate staff, coordinating, controlling and evaluating work, and motivating and building the development path of employees. Planning, developing and implementing purchasing strategies, negotiating, contracting and selecting suppliers, monitoring key performance indicators. Developing IT system and tools to increase efficiency and quality of work

acting purchasing manager May 2013 - March 2015 (1 year 11 months) Białe Błota

managing the team, organizing the work of own and subordinate staff, coordinating, controlling and evaluating work, and motivating and building the development path of employees. Planning, developing and implementing purchasing strategies, negotiating, contracting and selecting suppliers, monitoring key performance indicators. Developing IT system and tools to increase efficiency and quality of work

operational merchant specialist September 2010 - March 2015 (4 years 7 months)

Białe Błota

effective management of the purchasing process, price negotiations, optimization of costs and support of the company's strategic goals through effective activities in the purchasing department. Preparation and organization of training for lower level employees

merchant

January 2008 - August 2010 (2 years 8 months)

Białe Błota

monitoring and managing the supply chain to ensure the fluidity of the company's production processes, long-term planning, developing and maintaining positive relationships with suppliers and optimizing costs

opreational purchasing manager February 2009 - August 2009 (7 months)

Białe Błota

improve performance and plan training of team members, build and maintain long-term relationships with suppliers, optimize costs by analyzing and recommending changes

junior merchant

June 2007 - December 2007 (7 months)

Białe Błota, Kujawsko-Pomorskie, Polska

inventory monitoring, bid analysis and preparation of purchase orders, as well as reporting and supporting the company's purchasing processes

SPWIGOR Sławomir Posłuszny coach/ instructor

March 2016 - August 2022 (6 years 6 months)

Bydgoszcz

conducting sports classes in various age and skill categories, from general development classes [children] to specialized training classes for youth and adults.

Here I combine my passion, eternal love of sports and martial arts, and work with people.

Firma handlowa Caro S.Krawczyk customer service
September 2005 - May 2007 (1 year 9 months)

Bydgoszcz

direct customer service, inventory and delivery control, small bookkeeping

Bank-Serwis Sp. z o.o. service technician January 2005 - June 2005 (6 months)

Bydgoszcz

Service and upgrades of computer hardware and software, installation and upgrades of computer networks

F.H.U. Anmar

owner

January 2004 - December 2004 (1 year)

Bydgoszcz

own business activity, trade and services, trade/sales, transport services

Plafon Sp. z o.o.

invoice and sales clerk January 2002 - January 2004 (2 years 1 month)

Bydgoszcz

office management, control of company records, direct service to wholesale and retail customers, control and planning of warehouse and supplies, collection of receivables

Plafon s.c. Joanna Pachota i spółka

trader

February 1999 - December 2001 (2 years 11 months)

Bydgoszcz

wholesale and retail customer service and consulting, sales, customer acquisition, debt collection, delivery planning, full warehouse service, woodwork installation

Micronel Sp. z o.o.

warehouseman

June 1997 - January 1999 (1 year 8 months)

Bydgoszcz

customer service, full operational support of the warehouse

Education

Merito University

Database systems and data warehouse engineer, IT in business \cdot (October 2019 - March 2023)

Higher School of Economy in Bydgoszcz academic study, Manager's Academy · (2014 - 2015)